lifesabundance.com 2011-12-27

# Life's Abundance Privacy Policy

Life's Abundance has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for Life's Abundance.

Life's Abundance is the best place to shop for safe and effective premium supplements. We stand behind our products and guarantee your satisfaction with every order.

**Your credit card is safe with Life's Abundance.**

Every time you shop with Life's Abundance, your purchase is backed by a security guarantee. Our secure server encrypts (or scrambles) all of your personal information, including your name, address, credit card number, log-in name and password. Our encryption measures ensure that no one can access or use your personal information. Our 128-bit encryption is implemented with a secure certificate. Additionally, we do not retain any credit card information on our web server, so even in the rare event that someone should acquire your unique log-in name, your credit card information still could not be accessed.

**We guarantee your privacy**

At Life's Abundance, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Life's Abundance does not trade, sell or rent your personal information to other companies. It may be helpful for you to know how we use the information we collect:

We collect and aggregate non-personally identifiable information about shoppers browsing our site. We collect information such as your IP address, web browser type and operating system to enable us to provide shoppers with an enhanced shopping experience.

**Customers**

Our ordering process requires customers to give us contact information (like name, address, email and phone number), which we use to ship product orders and to contact you if necessary. As a direct sales company, our organization is based upon a network of our Independent Distributors, who own their own websites. Therefore, customers who register with us and do not have a Distributor will be assigned one. Life's Abundance will pass along the customer's contact information (Name, mailing address, phone number and email) and order information (item, quantity and price) to their assigned Distributor. Life's Abundance does NOT pass any financial information along to the sponsoring Distributor.

**What Information is being shared?**

We may need to share information with other companies during the course of business. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information for any secondary purposes. 

**Email**

We read every message sent and do our best to reply promptly to every one. We may file your comments to help us make future improvements to our web site, or we may review and discard the information contained in your email. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

Should we ever decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we might disclose it. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

There are two types of communications we send to our customers: essential and non-essential. Essential communications include, but are not limited to, order confirmation emails, emails containing tracking information for orders that have been shipped and Autoship reminder emails.

Non-essential emails include, but are not limited to, product announcements and general company information.

We provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential communications from us in three different ways.

1) You can send an email to support@lifesabundance.com  
2) You can call us toll-free at 877-387-4564   
3) You can reply to one of the non-essential emails, indicating you would like to be removed from our mailing list 

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

Field Representatives and Customers can click on My Account and follow the directions to update their information.

**Legal Disclaime** r

We may disclose personal information when required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or as otherwise required by law.

**Notification of Changes**

We will post changes in our privacy statement on this page whenever there is a change in our privacy policy.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [ support@lifesabundance.com](mailto:support@lifesabundance.com)
